[
    {
        "question": "ل ي ف ا ي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ا ي ك ي",
        "response": "مايكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ا و",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ي ت ش ي ل",
        "response": "ريتشيل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ي ت ش",
        "response": "تيتش"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش ا د و",
        "response": "شادو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ت ا ش ي",
        "response": "ايتاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ا ن م ا",
        "response": "هانما"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ي ر ل ي ن",
        "response": "كيرلين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و ل ي و س",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت و ب ي",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش و ت و",
        "response": "شوتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت و ج ا",
        "response": "توجا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز ا ر ا ك ي",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا ب و",
        "response": "سابو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي س",
        "response": "ايس"
    },
    {
        "question": "د ر ا ج و ن",
        "response": "دراجون"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن ا ن ا م ي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ي ن غ و ك و",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ي د",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ن ي",
        "response": "اني"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ي ن ا ت ا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن و ب ا ر ا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و ن و",
        "response": "يونو"
    },
    {ت
        "question": "م ا ك ي م ا",
        "response": "ماكيما"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا ن ي ك ي",
        "response": "كانيكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر و ج ر",
        "response": "روجر"
    },
    {
        "question": "د و ف ي",
        "response": "دوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش ا ن ك س",
        "response": "شانكس"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا س ت ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز ا ك",
        "response": "زاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "د ر ا ك ن",
        "response": "دراكن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا م ي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و س و ب",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ش و ب ر",
        "response": "تشوبر"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا ك و ر ا",
        "response": "ساكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا ن ج ي ر و",
        "response": "تانجيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك و ن ا ن",
        "response": "كونان"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا ت ا ك و ر ي",
        "response": "كاتاكوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا ن ج ي",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ب ي ج م ام",
        "response": "بيج مام"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا ي د و",
        "response": "كايدو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غ و ن",
        "response": "غون"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ي ل و ا",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ا ن",
        "response": "ران"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا س ك ي",
        "response": "ساسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز و ر و",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر و ب ي ن",
        "response": "روبين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن ا م ي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ل و ف ي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ن ا ر و ت و",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
       "question": "س و ن غ",
        "response": "سونغ"
    },
    {
       "question": "غ ا ت س",
        "response": "غاتس"
    },
    {
       "question": "س و ك و ن ا",
        "response": "سوكونا"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ر م ي ن",
        "response": "ارمين"
    },
    {
       "question": "ز ي ن ت س و",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
       "question": "م ي ك ا س ا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ي ر ي ن",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
       "question": "ن ي ز و ك و",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "م ي د و ر ي ا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
       "question": "م ي ت س و ر ي",
        "response": "ميتسوري"
    },
    {
       "question": "غ و ج و",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ب ا ي ن",
        "response": "باين"
    },
    {
       "question": "ش ي ز و ك ا",
        "response": "شيزوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "غ و ك و",
        "response": "غوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ك ي ر ا",
       "response": "اكيرا"
}
]
